I'm Peppa Pig
and this is my little brother, George
This is Mummy Pig
And this is Daddy Pig
Peppa Pig
"Mr. Scarecrow"
Today, Peppa and George
are visiting Granny and Grandpa Pig
-Hello, Grandpa Pig
Hello, Peppa
Hello, George
Grandpa, what are you doing?
I'm working in my garden
These seeds will grow into lovely flowers
All I do is put the seeds in the ground
and then cover the seeds with earth
Oh, where have the seeds gone?
The seeds are gone
That's strange
I'm sure I put the seeds here
Yes, Grandpa, we saw you
But the seeds aren't here now
Never mind, I'll just have to put some more seeds in
As I was saying
all I do is put the seeds in the ground
A bird is eating Grandpa's seeds
You can't eat my seeds!
Now I know where the seeds went
They're inside the bird's tummy
Two more birds have come to eat Grandpa's seeds
Oh, look
Shoo! Shoo!
What's all the noise?
Oh, Granny
The birds have eaten all my flower seeds
So we're shooing the birds away
Shooing them won't work, they'll just come back
Look
We need a scarecrow
What's a scarecrow?
A scarecrow is a man made of straw
that scares the birds away
That's a great idea, Granny
I'll go make one
Follow me
Bye-bye, birds
We're going to make a scarecrow now
This is Grandpa's garden shed
There are lots of things here to make a scarecrow with
First, we need two sticks and some string
Let's find them
Peppa has found some sticks
and George has found some string
Excellent
I'll tie the two sticks together to make the body
Grannny has found some straw and an old sack
Very good
I'll put the straw into the sack to make the head
Now we need to dress the scarecrow
Here's a bag of old clothes
George has found a dress
Silly George
Because Mr. Scarecrow doesn't wear dresses
Peppa has found a coat
Very good, Peppa
George has found a hat
Well done, George
Now Mr. Scarecrow needs a face
That's right
Would you and George like to draw his face?
Yes, please
George has drawn two eyes and a nose
And Peppa has drawn a mouth
That looks lovely
- Mr. Scarecrow is ready
- Hooray!
The birds are looking for Grandpa Pig's flower seeds to eat
Look, the birds are back
Don't worry, Peppa
Mr. Scarecrow will scare them away
It worked!
Mr. Scarecrow scared all the birds away
- Hooray!
Brilliant
The birds won't eat the flower seeds anymore
Oh, Grandpa Pig
The birds look so sad
Are they? They must be very hungry
That's why I brought this
What is it, Granny Pig?
It's a bird feeder
Grandpa Pig, can you give me some seeds?
Come along, birds, lunch is ready
Now the birds have their own seeds to eat
Hooray!
Now the birds are happy again
Peppa is very happy
that Grandpa Pig's seeds weren't eaten by the birds
But she is even happier
that the birds won't be hungry anymore